They lived here for almost ten years.
But there are things that have happened here.
We have the big Sean room, now there is no table and so left there.
They say that the mother sits there and is thrown all the way away and hits the fireplace.
They get very angry and then they throw out oath and Lorraine from here after this session.
We have the form of a little boy upstairs.
We have something that goes down in the basement.
You also talk about The Crooked Lady.
There is a child who has drawn a woman with crooked neck, much like being hung.
"There is no documented suicide in the house that someone has been hung"
It's really cool.
This will really be a great evening, the team has already started to carry in all the bags.
We are fixing all the cameras, so I think we start the investigation.
We go in.
Yes, then we are inside the house.
How does it feel?
I feel bad.
Yes you see ... we have talked a little off camera too ...
Already when we got here I started to get some headaches.
Then we have walked around the house, filmed a little behind the scenes and I just feel worse and worse, now I feel completely finished.
Yes, it is a powerful house, we talked about it initially, it has happened so much here.
Now we are going to form our own view, there are many who were here and investigated
And there are many stories.
Now we are here to see if it is true that people tell.
And I think we should have the background the story of the Perron family with us.
Because we know that happened, there is documented.
So we start from that.
Obvious.
How does it feel Johanna now when you entered the house here?
Dizzy and nausea.
I would be surprised if I was not vomited today.
Is it so bad?
Yes, it's the same feeling.
I do not feel good...
Wilma then?
I have never felt so affected.
I already feel that I am very affected.
I feel pressure over my head, I feel a little groggy.
Like I'm a little full.
Even nausea and like the eyes just hang.
So this ...
Exciting introduction.
And we should start now.
What was that?
Was there something that bit me there or?
Bet you?
Damn what it stuck.
Huh?
Like a damn needle.
I thought it was a wasp that bit me.
Was it so powerful?
Wait I have to hold on to me.
I was completely crazy.
Huh?
Is there anything?
Does it feel like a wasp stack you?
It was like someone is taking a needle and ...
There is nothing visible.
I may not have really got that paranormal feeling of the house, but I have done this so many times so I know it will come.
And you?
I have been walking around here and in some places these shivers.
And it's hot here, but it feels like someone is behind one and it gets ice cold, the hair just rises.
Goose bumps really.
We can say that it is not cold in here.
It is probably 27.28 degrees in the house here.
And you see how we are dressed.
It's not that we freeze.
But it is good that we go with only arms because then maybe we know these caresses, because they can touch one or caress one on their backs.
So we'll see what pops up.
And it happens in some places here in the building.
But what do you say, should we start?
And I think that first you go Niclas, me and Wilma, we walk around almost the whole house.
We just know and bring few tools.
And then you get ... did you see something?
Lennie came here ....
No, it's not you either.
No, Viktor, you have to remain there.
And this has happened far back, then you were doing black magic here, in this room.
So you have thrown spells and called up and down lots of evil forces.
I see a bunch of women who have been doing this and you have not really known what you have been doing.
So that here it is like an open portal, anyone can get in here, from the spirit world.
Or even the being can get in here.
And I feel that there is a lot of activity here, but precisely the spirits that belong to the house do not like to be here.
Without this, this is out.
Spirits that come from and into this portal then.
For the energies in the house are in different rooms here instead, because they do not like this with taking in anything or that it comes and goes energy.
I start an OVILUS so we have it.
Here I am very affected, it is rushing in my ears and it becomes like a lid.
And in here there is a lot of activity
I'll take a step in ..
It's like the energy in here .. I get to me that there are two energies here.
It wants to pull us in, but when we come in it disappears, it wants to run a game.
And I see that these two energies collaborate and will build up during the evening.
The more times you pass here, the stronger it will be.
A man and a woman, they belong together in some way.
They have made this their room and there is something about the books here, it is a special book.
Like he wants to warn, now now does not know what you are about to do.
Should we check out in the living room too?
The first thing I get to me here is that there is someone in the armchair behind it.
And that energy was already sitting here when I came in, it has been sitting here all the time.
And it's like that energy sticks to this surface and keeps a little track of who passes in and out.
And this energy communicates with the other spirits here and tells us that now they come in here and they will do this.
It is a male energy and it is like he blocks, that he finds out everything about us and sends it to them others.
It's the only one I get on this surface.
Is it a basement or something here?
It's a basement there.
Okay, because I've heard that it is shouted from there.
A woman with a knot in her hair sits waiting down there.
What threw the mother in the perron family ..
across the room ..
What this mother was in contact with, do you get who it might have where?
Because it is a case that you have talked about.
It was a form of portal, that it was not the spirits that were around, but it was something else.
What is it that has such power, I think.
Because it is almost five meters and being drawn or throwing requires a huge power.
Yes, I get like it is .. within the ritual world or how to call it, when you take from the good you take up from and when you take from the evil that digs down.
And I see pictures that you have been sitting in a circle, a bunch of women and that they have dug up.
I also see that you have been doing woodoo dolls.
Needles have been put in dolls to harm others.
And this that they have raised, it is an energy form I have never seen before.
It feels like it could be something demonic or something very, very dark.
I think it was interesting when you said it about needles and woodoo dolls, I thought about the introduction with your leg Niclas.
Needles, Stungen.
We are standing near this too.
Yes and when you mentioned it I get the number 7. I think we should remember the number 7 because it feels important, I can't link why now.
There is something about 7, when you started talking about it.
Now that we have been standing here, this was a long time that I knew, I have had them here the shivers, but right now it is like someone compressing the shoulder blades.
Like someone sitting or hanging on one.
That is why I get these shivers I think that something is behind.
I feel it as a weight in the shoulders.
And here in the chair it is like there is an older woman and she is not so despairing that there is something down here.
It's more like she's guarding, she's wished we would come in here.
But it feels very powerful, that it is linked to throwing someone down here.
We can say that child screams have been heard from there.
That it is like there is a child there.
There are voices in here and everything possible, so here you could sit down and be completely silent just.
Here I think they have done some challenge and tested here.
After all, I read in the book about hangers, moving, thrown when the Perron family was here.
They even got beaten with hangers in some wardrobes.
A voice is heard in the room.
What the hell was that?
Did you hear?
Wait I check.
Someone was talking.
A voice is heard in the room.
It is sick that it starts twice.
We start something more, I put on this.
It's a damn run here, it's everywhere.
What are you feeling?
What is up here?
I feel stressed and get stress up here.
I see children again, but I also see adult energies.
I see that there has been a family here, or a mom and a dad.
And that something dark has stood here and roared and frightened.
And that you have stepped forward and so you have come from the side and taken a strangle of people who have slept in this bed.
Then it is a huge portal from here and here, this is where everything runs comes.
Very much in that.
It's like the energies just pull me in there.
That we should go further.
Should we go further then?
Should we bring it too?
Bring PRS.
Here was the children's bedroom.
Those who slept in these beds went into that room, that's where the big sister always was, Andrea platform.
Just.
The previous owners took the theory of these soldiers.
That it may not be this wall but the wall that goes around.
And then they found five.
But they have not excavated them.
They don't really know, but they think it's there.
Should we try to go into the last room here too?
See if anything more happens.
And this should be Andrea Perron's bedroom.
The oldest in the siblings.
I get to see two peers in any case, two girls.
Now it is one of these girls who shows how she pulled out of this bed.
That she was lying in bed and then been pulled in her leg and pulled out.
She wants to show me that there is something here.
I also see a smaller girl, who gets out of bed and walks around the room, in circles.
Like she wakes up and then walking around and around like this.
Like something that has affected her and tried to take over her body.
Someone controls her?
Exactly.
The children have come in here because it thought it was a safe place.
But they have also seen a little boy coming.
Here.
Here it was a red lamp that flashed.
So hopefully the camera caught, no damn I was probably in the way of it.
I thought if it might be an aggregate that was shining, but it is not.
I will post paranormal Movement Alert.
We may hear it if something is moving out here.
I also have some motion sensors, who say Hello Welcome, so I post them here.
And we know that the woman has been seen walking here.
Now I have put it quite sensitive, in case something goes by there.
I'll try stamp next to it.
Here I put a Hello Welcome.
And so we have these cats toys.
We place everything in a line here.
We then have a surveillance camera over there and we go into the room there.
Here Johanna is one that you talked about, The Crooked Lady.
It is this that the children have drawn.
Yes, they have drawn her yes.
Who are you?
Do you want us to leave this room?
There is someone who moves me at the neck all the time, I get mad.
Are you behind Niclas now?
Continue touching the neck.
You can touch him.
I got a lot of headaches now.
Did you get a headache?
Here.
In the temple?
I don't really see.
Yes, the temples.
Okay.
Who is it that affects Viktor too?
I have to break.
What is it?
Someone pulls their fingers in the neck all the time, it's so damn uncomfortable.
Like this?
No, very loose.
Like this.
From one side to the other.
First, I think it might be a moth or something that landed on my neck.
But then you had seen it and said it.
Viktor got a damn headache.
Is it going well?
But now I've tested.
Now I want you to test this.
Do you want to hold it?
Directly we get green.
Good.
We get directly green.
You can do that.
Be strange.
It was really like, I didn't feel anyone pressed, but it felt like the head wanted that way.
And then when I was going to pick it up, it was sluggish.
We said your name once, then you say your name.
Yes, green.
I really heard Johanna.
I have a headache.
Shall we cancel and get up?
Or should you run up and get a Sony camera and do we drive a little neighbor?
We just drive in Nighvision here.
Okay.
We have switched to Nighvision because we do not have the usual camera we usually have.
For Viktor who has the camera has extreme headaches, we also have Lennie who has crashed totally, he is completely exhausted.
Wilma who also knows things, we have not been up for a while so we do not know how the others feel.
But we had to send away Viktor so he has to recover a little neighbor.
We drive down here.
I feel it still works for me.
Does it work for you?
Yes.
For you?
Same here.
No.
With piano.
I hear it!
I shiver!
Why do I hear this music?
I hope the camera catches this.
*Music Niclas Hear not caught by the camera*
Is it this lady with crooked neck who goes down here?
Green on it.
Directly there.
Thanks!
What shivers I have again, they come and go.
Do you want to go and stand there and look here?